Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of New York (ACUSNY); Records apap003
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planning Retreat, 1971-1991; 2; 4.66 cubic ft.
  - Seminar, 1978; 2 folders (Box 1 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 12-13)
    (The Federal Presence).
  - Seminar, 1979 (Box 1 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 14)
    (The State's Stake in Higher Education).
  - Rensselaervilles Past, 1971-1988 (Box 2 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 1)
    (list of discussed topics and speakers).
  - Retreat, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 2)
    (New Missions, Degree Patterns, New Student Groups, The Business Perspective, Faculty Training).
  - Retreat, 1981 (Box 2 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 3)
    (Perspectives on Higher Education in New York in the 1980s).
  - Retreat, 1982 (Box 2 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 4)
    (Liberal Education in the 1980s, Higher Education for High Technology).
  - Retreat, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 5)
    (Consider Ways to Link Public and Independent Institutions in Common Endeavor).
  - Retreat, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 6)
    (Shaping the Undergraduate Curriculum, Strengthening Presidential Leadership, ACUSNY's Future).
  - Retreat, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 7)
    (Presidential Task Force on Financial Policy Development toward a Definition of Quality Programs in Undergraduate Education, Centers on Advanced Technology).
  - Retreat, 1986 (Box 2 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 8)
    (Philosophical, Ideological, Practical and Political Aspects of Intersector Relationships).
  - Retreat, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 1)
    (Setting the Agenda for Higher Education, the Politics of Higher Education, the Down Side of Competition for Students, Issues Confronting Community College Presidents to Identify themes for ACUSNY Presidents'meeting throughout the year).
  - Retreat, 1988 (Box 3 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 2)
    (The Statewide Plan for Postsecondary Education, 1988, Higher Education and School Reform, Blacks & Latinos in Higher Education, Financing Higher Education in N.Y. State, Setting Priorities for N.Y. State Higher Education and Programs for ACUSNY).
  - President's Retreat Responses, 1988 (Box 3 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 3)
  - Retreat, 1989 (Box 3 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 4)
  - President's Retreat Survey and Correspondence, 1989 (Box 3 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 5)
  - President's Meeting, 02/05/1991 (Box 3 (2-Rensselaerville Summer Retreats/President's Planni), Folder 6)
- Annual Meetings, 1938-1991; 3; 6 cubic ft.
  Contains minutes, background information sent to members, correspondence, in particular to college and university presidents, membership lists, reports both by the Association's committees and by the University of ACUSNY the State of New York, and the State Education Department, and information concerning special meetings. Prominent topics include the State's need for a state university, 1947-1949; universal military training and manpower utilization, 1947-1949; planning for increased enrollment in 1954-1955 and the 1960s; state aid to private institutions, 1956-1960s; the Board of Regents Master Plan for Education, 1963; Constitutional Convention, 1967; Einstein-Schweitzer chairs, 1970s; improvement of the quality of student administrative services, 1981; perspectives of liberal education, 1984; women in higher education, 1987; reaching common interest in the public interest, 1989.
  Arranged chronologically by accession.
  - Meetings, 1938-1948 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 1)
  - Meetings, 1945-1946 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 2)
  - Meeting, 1947 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 3)
  - Meeting, 1948 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 4)
  - Meeting, 1949 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 5)
  - Meeting, 1949 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 6)
    Special meeting concerning proposed amendments to the State University Act.
  - Meeting, 1950 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 7)
  - Meeting, 1950 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 8)
  - Meeting, 1950 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 9)
    Special meeting concerning Master Plan for the State University.
  - Meeting, 1951 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 10)
  - Meeting, 1952 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 11)
  - Meeting, 1953 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 12)
  - Meeting, 1954 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 13)
  - Meeting, 1955 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 14)
  - Meeting, 1956 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 15)
  - Meeting, 1957 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 16)
  - Meeting, 1958 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 17)
  - Meeting, 1959 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 18)
  - Meeting, 1960 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 19)
  - Meeting, 1961; 2 folders (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 20-21)
  - Meeting, 1962 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 22)
  - Meeting, 1963 (Box 1 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 23)
  - Meeting, 1964 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 1)
  - Meeting, 1965 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 2)
  - Meeting, 1965 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 3)
    Special Meeting concerning two year/four year articulation.
  - Meeting, 1966; 2 folders (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 4-5)
  - Meeting, 1967 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 6)
  - Meeting, 1968 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 7)
  - Meeting, 1969 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 8)
  - Meeting, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 9)
  - Meeting, 1972-1973 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 10)
  - Meeting, 1973 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 11)
  - Meeting, 1974 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 12)
  - Meeting, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 13)
  - Meeting, 1977-1978 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 14)
  - Meeting, 1979 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 15)
  - Meeting, 1980 (Box 2 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 16)
  - Meeting, 1980 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 1)
  - Meeting, 1981 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 2)
  - Meeting, 1982 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 3)
  - Meeting, 1983 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 4)
  - Meeting, 1984 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 5)
  - Meeting, 1985 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 6)
  - Meeting, 1986 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 7)
  - Meeting, 1987 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 8)
  - Meeting, 1988 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 9)
  - Meeting, 1989 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 10)
  - Annual Business Meeting and Honorees, 1989 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 11)
  - Annual Meeting Planning, 1989 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 12)
  - Meeting, 1990 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 13)
  - Meeting, Honorees, 1990 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 14)
  - Meeting, Liberty Scholarships, 1990 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 15)
  - Meeting, 1991 November 12 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 16)
  - Legislation, 1949-1966; 1968-1992 (Box 3 (3-Annual Meetings), Folder 17)
    (Important legislative issues of temporary concern are noted in the folder list.).
- Legislation, 1946-1992; 4; 7.33 cubic ft.
  Contains correspondence to members, state politicians, the Governor's Office, and ACUSNY's lawyers; Association newsletters and legislation updates; copies of legislative documents; reports from the Board of Regents and the State Department of Education; statements by ACUSNY before the Joint Legislative Committee on Education. The series provides complete and detailed information about ACUSNY's concerns and activities. Records throughout the series document the Association's involvement with legislation concerning financial aid to students and institutions, taxation exemption, and state labor legislation. Other issues that are particularly well documented include state aid to private institutions, 1955-1956; the establishment of SUNY at Stony Brook, mid-1950s; establishment of a state corporation to provide financial aid to students, 1957; Amendment # 6, concerning the state's guarantee of bonds 1961; expansion of SUNY, 1964; CUNY financial crisis, 1966; campus unrest, 1969-1970; improvement of the State's Tuition Assistance Program, 1982; the Right-To-Know Law, 1986; crime on campus, 1989; the effect of the budget crists on the Einstein/Schweitzer Chairs, 1992.
  - Legislation, 1949-1950 (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 1)
    Education Practices Act (admissions policies).
  - Legislation, 1951 (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 2)
    Taxation exemption.
  - Legislation, 1952 (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 3)
    Educational television.
  - Legislation, 1953 (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 4)
    Subversion in educational institutions.
  - Legislation, 1954 (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - Legislation, 1955 (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 6)
    State Charities Registration legislation; State Dormitory Authority loans to private colleges and universities.
  - Legislation, 1956 (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 7)
    Establishment of a state college on Long Island (illustrates conflicts between state/private institutions).
  - Legislation, 1957 (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 8)
    Higher Education Assistance Corporation.
  - Legislation, 1958 (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 9)
    Fellowships for graduate students planning to teach at college level.
  - Legislation, 1959 (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 10)
    Nuclear Research Center at the University of Buffalo.
  - Legislation, 1960; 2 folders (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 11-12)
    Unemployment insurance tax.
  - Legislation, 1961; 4 folders (Box 1 (4-Legislation), Folder 13-16)
    Reference and research library resources; educational institutions compliance with state employment regulations; state aid to students at private institutions; Proposition # 6.
  - Legislation, 1962; 2 folders (Box 2 (4-Legislation), Folder 1-2)
    Unemployment benefits.
  - Legislation, 1963; 2 folders (Box 2 (4-Legislation), Folder 3-4)
  - Legislation, 1964; 2 folders (Box 2 (4-Legislation), Folder 5-6)
    Expansion of SUNY.
  - Legislation, 1965; 2 folders (Box 2 (4-Legislation), Folder 7-8)
    Use of Regents scholarships outside New York state; Education Practices Act (admissions practices; busing); Empire State university Expansion Program.
  - Legislation, 1966; 3 folders (Box 2 (4-Legislation), Folder 9-11)
    Unemployment insurance.
  - Legislation, 1968; 3 folders (Box 2 (4-Legislation), Folder 12-14)
    Bundy aid (state aid to private institutions).
  - Legislation, 1969; 3 folders (Box 2 (4-Legislation), Folder 15-17)
    Henderson Riot law; role of college and university administrators in quelling student disruptions.
  - Legislation, 1969; 2 folders (Box 2 (4-Legislation), Folder 18-19)
  - Legislation, 1970 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 1)
    Extension of State Dormitory Authority powers; Higher Education Opportunity Program;.
  - Legislation, 1971; 2 folders (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 2-3)
    Bundy aid; legislative control over faculty schedules.
  - Legislation, 1972 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 4)
    Einstein/Schweitzer chairs.
  - Legislation, 1973 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 5)
  - Legislation, 1974 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 6)
  - Legislation, 1975; 2 folders (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 7-8)
    Community college financing.
  - Legislation, 1976; 2 folders (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 9-10)
    Tuition Assistance Program (TAP): federal legislation.
  - Legislation, 1977; 2 folders (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 11-12)
    Graduate fellowships.
  - Legislation, 1978 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 13)
    TAP.
  - Legislation, 1979 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 14)
    Hazing.
    Department of Health Immunization Requirement, 1989-92.
  - Legislation, 1980 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 15)
  - Legislation, 1981 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 16)
  - Legislation, 1982 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 17)
  - Legislation, 1983 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 18)
  - Legislation, 1984 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 19)
  - Legislation, 1986 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 20)
  - Legislation, 1989 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 21)
  - Legislation, 1990 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 22)
  - Legislation, 1991 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 23)
  - Legislation, 1992 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 24)
  - Legislative Commission on Science and Technology, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (4-Legislation), Folder 25)
- Correspondence and Subject Files, 1938-1992; 5; 13.32 cubic ft.
  Contains general correspondence, 1938-1948, correspondence with foundations and out-of-state associations, and reports of ACUSNY committees, meeting minutes, correspondence and reports of the Commission of Independent Colleges and Universities, 1976, 1982-1984, membership lists, 1948-1962, 1965-1979; incorporation petition, 1972. Also contains information concerning the State Scholarship Program, 1950; two year degree colleges; the central campus issue, 1957; graduate education, 1958; CUNY, 1976; Long Range Planning conference, 1979; the State Education Department, 1979-1980, 1983-1984, 1988; state funding for higher education, 1991; performance standards for postsecundary and adult vocational education programs, 1992.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Adams, John Crawford, 1949-1950 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Admissions Crisis, 1958 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Admissions Policies--Report, [1947?] (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Blaney, Joseph, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Board of Regents, 1957-1959 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Case, Everett, 1949-1950; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 6-7)
  - Central Campus Issue--Clippings, 1957 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Clarkson College--Tax Case, 1949-1950 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Commission for Independent Colleges and Universities, 1976 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Commission for Independent Colleges and Universities, 1982 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Commission for Independent Colleges and Universities, 1983; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 12-13)
  - Commission for Independent Colleges and Universities, 1984 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Commission on Non-Tax Supported Colleges and Universities, Undated (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Admissions Questionnaires, 1958 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Budget, 1957-1958 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Regional Meeting, 1957 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Committee on Community Education, 1946-1947 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Committee on Community Education, 1947-1949; 3 folders (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 22-24)
  - Committee on Membership, 1950 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Committee on Need for a State University, 1946-1948 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Committee on School Curricula, 1949-1950 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Committee on Teacher Education, 1945-1946 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Committee on Teacher Education--Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Committee on Teacher Education--Reports, 1941-1942; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 30-31)
  - Committee to Study Secondary School Records, [1947?] (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Community Colleges, Correspondence, 1964; 1983-1986 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Computer Seminar for Presidents, 1986 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Concordia College: Tax Case, 1950 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Correspondence--General, 1938-1940 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Correspondence--General, 1941; 2 folders (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 37-38)
  - Correspondence--General, 1942 (Box 1 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Correspondence--General, 1943 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence--General, 1944 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence--General, 1945 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence--General, 1946 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence--General, 1947-1948 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Council on Higher Education, 1958 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - CUNY, 1976 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Education Practices Act, 1948; 2 folders (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 8-9)
  - Education Practices Act, 1949 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Education Practices Bill, 1947 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Engineering & Scientific Students: Deferments, 1945 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Engineering Enrollments: Press Release, Undated (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Fennell, Colleen, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Future of Higher and Professional Education in New York State, Reports I-XXIV, University of the State of NY, State Education Department, Office of the, 1954-1955 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Governor's Conference, 1946 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Graduate Education: Study, 1958 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - History, Undated (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Incorporation: Study, 1958 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Ingalls, Les: Correspondence, 1957 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Loans/Scholarships: Questionnaire, 1959 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Long Range Planning Conference, 1949 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Membership Lists, 1948-1962 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Membership Lists, 1965-1979 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1957-1958; 2 folders (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 25-26)
  - Reference: Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Speeches, 1957-1959 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - State Education Department, 1979-1980 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - State Education Department, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - State Education Department, 1988 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - State School Program, 1950 (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Two Year Degree Program, Undated (Box 2 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - ACE/NIP, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - ACUSNY: Mutual Assistance Program Survey, 1985 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - ACUSNY Review, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - ACUSNY Transition, 1984-1987 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Academic Contacts, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - AIDS, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Albany Forum on Postsecondary Education Financing, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting-Honorees-Locations-Attendance-Miscellaneous Information, Undated (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Archives, 1988-1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Assessment, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Business Council, Meeting with, 1989-1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Carnegie/AAHE Presidents' Forum on Teaching as Profession, 1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Chronicle, 1989; 1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - College Boards, 1988-1989; 1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - College Costs, 1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - College Savings Plans, 1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - College Savings Plans, Out of New York State, 1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Community College Transfers, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Community Colleges - Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Corporate Academic Workshop, 1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Correspondence with ACUSNY Board of Trustees, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, general, 1988-1992; 2 folders (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 23-24)
  - Correspondence with Ira Bloom, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Correspondence with Jay Hershenson, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, Marburger (his out), 1988-1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Correspondence with Marburger, 1989-1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Correspondence with ACUSNY President Jack Marburger, III, 1988-1989 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Correspondence - Miscellaneous Membership, 1989-1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Correspondence with President Roche, 1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Correspondence with Steering Committee, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Department of Labor, 1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Division of Women, 1990-1991 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - E, 1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Economy and Higher Education, 1988-1990 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Executive Committee Trustees, 1974/1975-1985/1986 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Faculty/Graduate Education, 1987-1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Governors Executive Forum Critical Technologies for the 21st Century, 1992 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Guidebook to Colleges, 1988 (Box 3 (5-Correspondence and Subject Files), Folder 40)